[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 5, "question": "Probably -- one of the \"Night at the Museum\" maybe?", "question_tokens": ["Probably", "--", "one", "of", "the", "``", "Night", "at", "the", "Museum", "''", "maybe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "CD", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "''", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 6, "answer": "\"Meet the Fockers.\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Meet", "the", "Fockers", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "Advantage or disadvantage?", "question_tokens": ["Advantage", "or", "disadvantage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "I think there's an advantage because you know what you're going into.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "'s", "an", "advantage", "because", "you", "know", "what", "you", "'re", "going", "into", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last eight years"], "PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 20, "question": "What's going on with your country?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "going", "on", "with", "your", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 21, "answer": "I feel like we've inherited a bad situation over the last eight years and Obama is in a very tough position.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "like", "we", "'ve", "inherited", "a", "bad", "situation", "over", "the", "last", "eight", "years", "and", "Obama", "is", "in", "a", "very", "tough", "position", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 44, "question": "You hate doing these things, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "hate", "doing", "these", "things", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Whoo!", "answer_tokens": ["Whoo", "!"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "What is the idea of me?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "idea", "of", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "I mean, it's not really you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "really", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Piers, when did it begin, the need to delve deep into people's souls?", "question_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "when", "did", "it", "begin", ",", "the", "need", "to", "delve", "deep", "into", "people", "'s", "souls", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "I like doing that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "doing", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "You do?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "And, actually, you like doing it.", "answer_tokens": ["And", ",", "actually", ",", "you", "like", "doing", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Do you like the pressure of having to be funny?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "the", "pressure", "of", "having", "to", "be", "funny", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "No, not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "Do you know which of your 30 movies has grossed the most?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "which", "of", "your", "30", "movies", "has", "grossed", "the", "most", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WDT", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Not \"Envy,\" I know that.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "``", "Envy", ",", "''", "I", "know", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "JJ", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "JJR", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "What are your three worst movies?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "three", "worst", "movies", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "CD", "JJS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Oh, gosh, there's more than three.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "gosh", ",", "there", "'s", "more", "than", "three", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "What's been the biggest turkey of your life?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "been", "the", "biggest", "turkey", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "TILLER: Oh, in terms of money, I'd probably like -- you like that movie.", "answer_tokens": ["TILLER", ":", "Oh", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "money", ",", "I", "'d", "probably", "like", "--", "you", "like", "that", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Probably one of the -- \"The Night at the Museum,\" maybe?", "question_tokens": ["Probably", "one", "of", "the", "--", "``", "The", "Night", "at", "the", "Museum", ",", "''", "maybe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", ":", "``", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "\"Meet the Fockers.\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Meet", "the", "Fockers", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "What did you do, Focker?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "do", ",", "Focker", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Nothing.", "answer_tokens": ["Nothing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Focker"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Debbie", "Greg"]}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "What's the sign for sour milk?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "sign", "for", "sour", "milk", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "That's because it's from Debbie's left breast, Greg.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "because", "it", "'s", "from", "Debbie", "'s", "left", "breast", ",", "Greg", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "What does that tell you about our culture?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "that", "tell", "you", "about", "our", "culture", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "It tells you about anything.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "tells", "you", "about", "anything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "What was it like working with De Niro?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "working", "with", "De", "Niro", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "At first, it was pretty intimidating because I'm such a fan of his, and his movies from my generation growing up are so iconic.", "answer_tokens": ["At", "first", ",", "it", "was", "pretty", "intimidating", "because", "I", "'m", "such", "a", "fan", "of", "his", ",", "and", "his", "movies", "from", "my", "generation", "growing", "up", "are", "so", "iconic", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Advantage or disadvantage?", "question_tokens": ["Advantage", "or", "disadvantage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Well, it depends what you're talking about.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "depends", "what", "you", "'re", "talking", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "VBG", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "But then there's also -- then you have to kind of make your own way and, you know?", "question_tokens": ["But", "then", "there", "'s", "also", "--", "then", "you", "have", "to", "kind", "of", "make", "your", "own", "way", "and", ",", "you", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "Yes, I mean, at first, what I meant was I can see how having parents who are in the business can be helpful, advice and everything else.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "at", "first", ",", "what", "I", "meant", "was", "I", "can", "see", "how", "having", "parents", "who", "are", "in", "the", "business", "can", "be", "helpful", ",", "advice", "and", "everything", "else", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "What values did they instill in you, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "values", "did", "they", "instill", "in", "you", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "My dad's a pretty hardworking guy.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "dad", "'s", "a", "pretty", "hardworking", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "No, that's not true.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "that", "'s", "not", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "CC", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Are there some you don't let them watch?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "there", "some", "you", "do", "n't", "let", "them", "watch", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "Well, they -- I have -- personally, they're not that interested in watching my -- I'm not going to try to get them to watch, you know, something about marriage and like that, because they're 9 and 6.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "--", "I", "have", "--", "personally", ",", "they", "'re", "not", "that", "interested", "in", "watching", "my", "--", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "try", "to", "get", "them", "to", "watch", ",", "you", "know", ",", "something", "about", "marriage", "and", "like", "that", ",", "because", "they", "'re", "9", "and", "6", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Are they showing signs of comedic genius?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "showing", "signs", "of", "comedic", "genius", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "TILLER: They are -- they're very theatrical children.", "answer_tokens": ["TILLER", ":", "They", "are", "--", "they", "'re", "very", "theatrical", "children", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Do you like being a father?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "being", "a", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "I love being a father, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "being", "a", "father", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Yes, I mean, in terms of your filming schedule, how do you juggle that with being a dad?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "your", "filming", "schedule", ",", "how", "do", "you", "juggle", "that", "with", "being", "a", "dad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "You have to figure out how you're going to do it so that you make sure that you have the family time.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "have", "to", "figure", "out", "how", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "do", "it", "so", "that", "you", "make", "sure", "that", "you", "have", "the", "family", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "Yes, what do you really think of it?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "what", "do", "you", "really", "think", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "I think it's -- I think it's a tough business.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "--", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "tough", "business", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Is the dream what you hoped it would be?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "dream", "what", "you", "hoped", "it", "would", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "The dream's hollow and empty, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "dream", "'s", "hollow", "and", "empty", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Is it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "Hollow and empty and cold.", "answer_tokens": ["Hollow", "and", "empty", "and", "cold", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Are they?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "They can be.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "can", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 235, "question": "Present company exempted?", "question_tokens": ["Present", "company", "exempted", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 236, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "There's no evidence of alcoholism, major drug abuse?", "question_tokens": ["There", "'s", "no", "evidence", "of", "alcoholism", ",", "major", "drug", "abuse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "It's well hidden.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "well", "hidden", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brian Grazer"]}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "Anything to chip away at that halo?", "question_tokens": ["Anything", "to", "chip", "away", "at", "that", "halo", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "TO", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "Brian Grazer and I are having an affair.", "answer_tokens": ["Brian", "Grazer", "and", "I", "are", "having", "an", "affair", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Is it going well?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "going", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "I'm in love with his hair.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "in", "love", "with", "his", "hair", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "Ben Stiller's latest movie, \"Tower Heist,\" what were you laughing there?", "question_tokens": ["Ben", "Stiller", "'s", "latest", "movie", ",", "``", "Tower", "Heist", ",", "''", "what", "were", "you", "laughing", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJS", "NN", ",", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "I was laughing -- you always show the person watching themselves.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "laughing", "--", "you", "always", "show", "the", "person", "watching", "themselves", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben Stiller"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "You excited about this one, \"Tower Heist\"?", "question_tokens": ["You", "excited", "about", "this", "one", ",", "``", "Tower", "Heist", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "TILLER: I'm really excited because it's actually a -- it's a genre movie that I've never been in, a heist movie.", "answer_tokens": ["TILLER", ":", "I", "'m", "really", "excited", "because", "it", "'s", "actually", "a", "--", "it", "'s", "a", "genre", "movie", "that", "I", "'ve", "never", "been", "in", ",", "a", "heist", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "What's going on with your country?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "going", "on", "with", "your", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Oh, wow.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "RBR", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "JJR", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "He disappointed you, Obama?", "question_tokens": ["He", "disappointed", "you", ",", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "I -- I'm a -- I'm disappointed that we haven't seen more bold decisions from him and a willingness, I think, to maybe stick to more of what he had, in his campaign, had said in terms of what he was willing to do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--", "I", "'m", "a", "--", "I", "'m", "disappointed", "that", "we", "have", "n't", "seen", "more", "bold", "decisions", "from", "him", "and", "a", "willingness", ",", "I", "think", ",", "to", "maybe", "stick", "to", "more", "of", "what", "he", "had", ",", "in", "his", "campaign", ",", "had", "said", "in", "terms", "of", "what", "he", "was", "willing", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Are you finding them good -- of comedic value?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "finding", "them", "good", "--", "of", "comedic", "value", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "JJ", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 358, "question": "Are you wary of discussing this?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "wary", "of", "discussing", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "I am wary, yes, because I, again --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "wary", ",", "yes", ",", "because", "I", ",", "again", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Maher"]}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "-- in your Google hit list?", "question_tokens": ["--", "in", "your", "Google", "hit", "list", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "I don't -- I don't see myself as a political commentator or a comedian in any way, though I do enjoy Bill Maher's show.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "see", "myself", "as", "a", "political", "commentator", "or", "a", "comedian", "in", "any", "way", ",", "though", "I", "do", "enjoy", "Bill", "Maher", "'s", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Google"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Well, they are quite funny, some of these Republicans, don't they?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "are", "quite", "funny", ",", "some", "of", "these", "Republicans", ",", "do", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Yes, but when you watch him as a serious presidential candidate, what do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", "when", "you", "watch", "him", "as", "a", "serious", "presidential", "candidate", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "I think that I can't imagine him being president.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "I", "ca", "n't", "imagine", "him", "being", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "-- your fellow countrymen?", "question_tokens": ["--", "your", "fellow", "countrymen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "I mean, I think -- I would think that Mitt Romney would have more of a chance at this point.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "I", "think", "--", "I", "would", "think", "that", "Mitt", "Romney", "would", "have", "more", "of", "a", "chance", "at", "this", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "What about Herman Cain, the pizza guy?", "question_tokens": ["What", "about", "Herman", "Cain", ",", "the", "pizza", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "I saw him on the \"Meet the Press,\" and I was not impressed.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "saw", "him", "on", "the", "``", "Meet", "the", "Press", ",", "''", "and", "I", "was", "not", "impressed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Because he wouldn't answer questions when they started asking about foreign policy, he would just say, \"I'm going to talk to my advisors.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "he", "would", "n't", "answer", "questions", "when", "they", "started", "asking", "about", "foreign", "policy", ",", "he", "would", "just", "say", ",", "``", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "talk", "to", "my", "advisors", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "I mean, why does it still motivate you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "why", "does", "it", "still", "motivate", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "I just -- I went down there for the first time before the earthquake, and it was in such a bad situation that I wanted to try to do something to help there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "--", "I", "went", "down", "there", "for", "the", "first", "time", "before", "the", "earthquake", ",", "and", "it", "was", "in", "such", "a", "bad", "situation", "that", "I", "wanted", "to", "try", "to", "do", "something", "to", "help", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "What do you feel about people who criticize celebrities for helping the stuff like that, the criticism being you're just doing it to promote yourself?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "people", "who", "criticize", "celebrities", "for", "helping", "the", "stuff", "like", "that", ",", "the", "criticism", "being", "you", "'re", "just", "doing", "it", "to", "promote", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Well, I think everybody's entitled to their opinion.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "everybody", "'s", "entitled", "to", "their", "opinion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "You must be sick of it, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "must", "be", "sick", "of", "it", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "Not at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Are you being honest?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "being", "honest", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Sometimes I'm sick of it.", "answer_tokens": ["Sometimes", "I", "'m", "sick", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 437, "question": "-- with the passage of time?", "question_tokens": ["--", "with", "the", "passage", "of", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 438, "answer": "Wait a minute.", "answer_tokens": ["Wait", "a", "minute", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "I'm affectionate toward the movie or the passage of time in general?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "affectionate", "toward", "the", "movie", "or", "the", "passage", "of", "time", "in", "general", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Both.", "answer_tokens": ["Both", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "What do you think of Rick Perry?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "Rick", "Perry", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "We're coming to that.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "coming", "to", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Perry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 456, "question": "What do you think of Herman Cain?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "Herman", "Cain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Everything he said, I -- you know --", "answer_tokens": ["Everything", "he", "said", ",", "I", "--", "you", "know", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 466, "question": "I don't know, 11?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "11", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "What's he -- what's he like --", "answer_tokens": ["What", "'s", "he", "--", "what", "'s", "he", "like", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Is this true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "Now it comes out.", "answer_tokens": ["Now", "it", "comes", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Any tantrums?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "tantrums", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "How have you avoided the cliche Hollywood trap of endless divorces?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "avoided", "the", "cliche", "Hollywood", "trap", "of", "endless", "divorces", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Endless divorces.", "answer_tokens": ["Endless", "divorces", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 514, "question": "How do -- does one do it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "--", "does", "one", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", ":", "VBZ", "CD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "We both sort of come from similar backgrounds as both our parents were...", "answer_tokens": ["We", "both", "sort", "of", "come", "from", "similar", "backgrounds", "as", "both", "our", "parents", "were", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matthew"], "LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Yes, and we -- we both grew up around it in New York and Matthew was successful earlier than I was.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "we", "--", "we", "both", "grew", "up", "around", "it", "in", "New", "York", "and", "Matthew", "was", "successful", "earlier", "than", "I", "was", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "What happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "I just froze up.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "froze", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joe Pesci"]}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "What happened with that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "happened", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Joe Pesci, he just -- he just freaked me out or something.", "answer_tokens": ["Joe", "Pesci", ",", "he", "just", "--", "he", "just", "freaked", "me", "out", "or", "something", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Are you good at auditions?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "good", "at", "auditions", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "He was just good.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "just", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "...monstrous box office megastar?", "question_tokens": ["...", "monstrous", "box", "office", "megastar", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "It's like a nightmare.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "like", "a", "nightmare", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "No chink in the armor that we could dwell on?", "question_tokens": ["No", "chink", "in", "the", "armor", "that", "we", "could", "dwell", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Not that I have found.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "that", "I", "have", "found", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "He's kidding, right?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "kidding", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "You get shot in the head it's over.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "get", "shot", "in", "the", "head", "it", "'s", "over", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Then what you going to do?", "question_tokens": ["Then", "what", "you", "going", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Die.", "answer_tokens": ["Die", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "EX", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Is there anybody, do you think, in Hollywood left who's got a better record than that?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anybody", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "in", "Hollywood", "left", "who", "'s", "got", "a", "better", "record", "than", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "WP", "POS", "VBD", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "I'm sure there is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sure", "there", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Would he beat that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "he", "beat", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "Can you understand it?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "understand", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Not entirely, because they're not -- they don't have a specific message that they're saying.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "entirely", ",", "because", "they", "'re", "not", "--", "they", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "specific", "message", "that", "they", "'re", "saying", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Madoff"]}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "Do you have a -- did you have a character in mind?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "--", "did", "you", "have", "a", "character", "in", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "Well, Madoff, we did.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Madoff", ",", "we", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "Would you accept that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "accept", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "We -- we're on the artist side so we -- (inaudible) table.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "--", "we", "'re", "on", "the", "artist", "side", "so", "we", "--", "(", "inaudible", ")", "table", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Is Hollywood as ruthless as people say it is?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "Hollywood", "as", "ruthless", "as", "people", "say", "it", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "It's hard to understand how it works.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "to", "understand", "how", "it", "works", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brian"]}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ":", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "How -- how -- how important -- let me ask you Brett, how important is someone like Ben to a movie now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "--", "how", "--", "how", "important", "--", "let", "me", "ask", "you", "Brett", ",", "how", "important", "is", "someone", "like", "Ben", "to", "a", "movie", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", ":", "WRB", ":", "WRB", "JJ", ":", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "Put it this way, we developed the movie -- Brian and I developed the movie for several years.", "answer_tokens": ["Put", "it", "this", "way", ",", "we", "developed", "the", "movie", "--", "Brian", "and", "I", "developed", "the", "movie", "for", "several", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brett", "Ben"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 704, "question": "Yes, Eddie pitched Brian and I the idea and I've been wanting to work with him since I was a kid, I've been such a big fan, and Brian had done maybe five -- five or six movies with him?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Eddie", "pitched", "Brian", "and", "I", "the", "idea", "and", "I", "'ve", "been", "wanting", "to", "work", "with", "him", "since", "I", "was", "a", "kid", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "such", "a", "big", "fan", ",", "and", "Brian", "had", "done", "maybe", "five", "--", "five", "or", "six", "movies", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "CD", ":", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 705, "answer": "Yes, a total of six movies.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "a", "total", "of", "six", "movies", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eddie", "Brian", "Brian"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "DT", ",", "DT", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 718, "question": "Was Ben not available?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "Ben", "not", "available", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 719, "answer": "Ben wasn't -- no, this was after we wrapped the movie.", "answer_tokens": ["Ben", "was", "n't", "--", "no", ",", "this", "was", "after", "we", "wrapped", "the", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 732, "question": "What was he like to work with, Matthew?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "like", "to", "work", "with", ",", "Matthew", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 733, "answer": "He was, you know, he's kind of -- since I started is right about the time when he started so I've grown up on him.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", ",", "you", "know", ",", "he", "'s", "kind", "of", "--", "since", "I", "started", "is", "right", "about", "the", "time", "when", "he", "started", "so", "I", "'ve", "grown", "up", "on", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matthew"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":"], "qSentId": 741, "question": "Did you -- did even someone like you feel intimidated?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "--", "did", "even", "someone", "like", "you", "feel", "intimidated", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "Sure...", "answer_tokens": ["Sure", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eddie"]}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", ":", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 743, "question": "Working with someone like Eddie?", "question_tokens": ["Working", "with", "someone", "like", "Eddie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 744, "answer": "...yes, because Eddie has been -- he's iconic for -- for, you know, the last 25 years.", "answer_tokens": ["...", "yes", ",", "because", "Eddie", "has", "been", "--", "he", "'s", "iconic", "for", "--", "for", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "last", "25", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eddie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "If you could cast one leading man in the last movie you ever make, who would it be?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "could", "cast", "one", "leading", "man", "in", "the", "last", "movie", "you", "ever", "make", ",", "who", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "Oh my God.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "my", "God", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 796, "question": "Can you name someone?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "name", "someone", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 797, "answer": "I can name some dead ones.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "name", "some", "dead", "ones", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Daniel Day-Lewis"]}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 803, "question": "Who would you say?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 804, "answer": "I am a big Daniel Day-Lewis fan.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "a", "big", "Daniel", "Day-Lewis", "fan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 829, "question": "This was in The Freshman, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "was", "in", "The", "Freshman", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 830, "answer": "This was in The Freshman.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "was", "in", "The", "Freshman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 832, "question": "And you got in a stage of his career when he was getting fed lines through his ear, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "got", "in", "a", "stage", "of", "his", "career", "when", "he", "was", "getting", "fed", "lines", "through", "his", "ear", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 833, "answer": "Well, you seem to be getting fed lines.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "seem", "to", "be", "getting", "fed", "lines", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ben", "Eddie"]}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NNS", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 855, "question": "So he was the best you've seen you think?", "question_tokens": ["So", "he", "was", "the", "best", "you", "'ve", "seen", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 856, "answer": "...yes, well, you know, and Ben and Eddie and there are a lot of great ones.", "answer_tokens": ["...", "yes", ",", "well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "and", "Ben", "and", "Eddie", "and", "there", "are", "a", "lot", "of", "great", "ones", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 870, "question": "RAZER: Are you?", "question_tokens": ["RAZER", ":", "Are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 871, "answer": "In a movie.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "a", "movie", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 874, "question": "The Robert Zemeckis movie?", "question_tokens": ["The", "Robert", "Zemeckis", "movie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 875, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Robert Zemeckis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 876, "question": "Is it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 877, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111105pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 891, "question": "I think it's going to be a great comeback for Eddie Murphy and you guys, I think you've -- you've -- it's a great (inaudible) film and it's hard, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "a", "great", "comeback", "for", "Eddie", "Murphy", "and", "you", "guys", ",", "I", "think", "you", "'ve", "--", "you", "'ve", "--", "it", "'s", "a", "great", "(", "inaudible", ")", "film", "and", "it", "'s", "hard", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 892, "answer": "Yes it is.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Eddie Murphy"]}}]